Guide to the Scott Elledge papers,1966-1984.
Scott Elledge papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scott Elledge papers, 1920-1986.
14/12/3592
Scott Elledge
1.4 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Correspondence, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes course material, correspondence and material from his book on E.B. White.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of English, Cornell University from 1962-1984.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes course material, correspondence and material from his book on E.B. White.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Elledge, Scott; E.B. White(Elwyn Brooks), 1899-1985.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University.English Dept.
Subjects:
College teachers.; English literature--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Elledge Vita, 1962-1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- E.B. White Carleton Lecture (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Book & Bowl Banquet, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1937-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bangkok Talk, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- White - Fred Lecture (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Rock Dove (Box 1, Folder 7)
- How to Write Like E.B. White (Box 1, Folder 8)
- How to Write Like E.B. White (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The Lady is Cold (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Principles for Principals, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- White - Cornell Lecture, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- E.B. White - "Alice Through the Cellophane" (Box 1, Folder 13)
- E.B. White-Related Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Andy White at Cornell, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- White to Ross, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- How to Write Like EBW (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Balto Interviews, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Interview with Mrs. Thurber, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- White, Freud, Proust, Nostalgia, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Wolcott Gibbs: "Theory and Practice of Editing New Yorker Articles" (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Rosanne Magdol, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Interview with Alphonse Smith, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Interview with Everett Adams, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Interview with Bishop (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Interview with Lillian (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Interview with Clara White (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Interview with Roger Angell, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Interview with Stanley White, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Interview with Mrs. B. Adams (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Sullivan Letters, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Interview with Nancy and Louise Stableford, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Liane's Notes, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- White - Biographical Notes, Interview with Joel, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- EBW Bibliography, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Letters: EBW to Kay S. White, 1934-1968 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Ross and New Yorker, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- White - Misc. Peripheral Clippings, 1920-1939 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- White - Articles about (Box 1, Folder 39)
- EBW Correspondence, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- W.W. Norton Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Stanford Library Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Class of '21 Talk, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- EBW Reviews, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- EBW & New Yorker Clippings, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Knox Burger, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- EBW - Correspondence about, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- English 315, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Evanston Teachers (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Singapore - Java - Bali (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Trip Expenses (Box 2, Folder 2)
- English Ab (Box 2, Folder 3)
- English 492 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- English 250 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- English 250, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- English 227, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Shakespeare, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Univ. of Minnesota Press (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence about the book (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Harvard Summer School, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Dramatics (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Miami Meeting (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Lit. Criticism, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Shakespeare, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- English 271, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- English 673, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Pictures and Book Review, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Various Course Material (Box 2, Folder 19)